Guide to the Richard Smalley papers, 1943-2007, bulk 1990-2005 MS 490
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XIII: Lectures, Presentations, and Conferences, 1997-2005; 249265
  - Science Committee Hearing on Nanotechnology, March 19-20, 2003; 249382 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Texas Heart Institute, March 21, 2003; 249381 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Joint DARPA/NRO Assembly Space Project, March 25-27, 2003; 249380 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Role Model Program, March 29, 2003; 249379 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - National Nanotechnology Initiative, "Nanotechnology for Energy Prosperity", April 2-4, 2003; 249378 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - CCR Annual Meeting, "Nanotechnology, Energy, and People", April 5-8, 2003; 249377 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Presidential Seach Committee Meeting, April 7, 2003; 249376 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Distinguished Lecturer, Sam Houston State University, April 9, 2003; 249375 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Excellence in Science Luncheon/Judy Allen, April 11, 2003; 249374 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - DeCoursey Lecture, Trinity University, "Buckytubes! New Applications of Nanotechnology", April 16, 2003; 249373 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - NRC Natural Gas Demand and Supply Projections Workshop, April 21, 2003; 249372 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Houston Museum of Natural Science: The Centennial Exhibition of the Nobel Prize, April 22, 2003; 249371 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - URETI-External Advisory Board (cancelled), April 23, 2003; 249370 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Rand Report to the President, April 30, 2003; 249369 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Meeting with Canadian Minister Richard Neufeld, May 1, 2003; 249368 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Energy Nanotech Workshop (BIPP), May 2-5, 2003; 249367 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - CBEN Media, May 5-6, 2003; 249366 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Nanotechnology Foundation of Texas Breakfast, May 7, 2003; 249365 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Rice Alumni Honors Dinner, May 10, 2003; 249364 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Baker Institute of Public Policy Round Table, May 12, 2003; 249363 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Olof Hjortstam Meeting, May 14, 2003; 249362 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer Honorary Degree, May 17, 2003; 249361 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Soldier Nanotechnologies, "The Impact of Nanotechnology", May 22, 2003; 249360 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - NASA-JSC & NIST Workshop, "Nanotube Applications and the Need for Standards", May 27-29, 2003; 249359 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - DOE Basic Energy Sciences Advisory Committee (BESAC) Meeting, May 28, 2003; 249358 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Iran Thomas Symposium (BES Science), "Scientific Grand Challenges for the Energy Mission", May 29, 2003; 249357 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Center for Integrated Nanotechnologies Workshop, June 4-6, 2003; 249356 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Nanotech and Energy for Applications, June 10, 2003; 249355 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - NNI Nanomaterials Workshop, "What's New at the Nanoscale", June 11, 2003; 249354 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - IBM, "Brave New World of Buckytubes", June 16, 2003; 249353 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Jortner 70th Birthday Symposium, June 16-17, 2003; 249352 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Hydrogen Storage Pre-Solicitation Meeting, June 19, 2003; 249351 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Scientific Advisory Committee, Center for Nanophase Material Sciences (cancelled), June 19-20, 2003; 249350 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - National Space and Missile Materials Symposium, June 23, 2003; 249349 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Milby/NSBRI, June 24, 2003; 249348 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - National Renewable Energy Laboratory (NREL) Distinguished Lecture, "Buckyballs, Buckytubes, and Energy", June 26-27, 2003; 249347 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Aspen Global Change Institute, "Our Energy Challenge", July 5-12, 2003; 249346 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Texas Institute for Intelligent Bio-Nano Materials, July 14-15, 2003; 249345 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Attucks Middle School, "Top 10 Problems in the Next 50 Years", July 18, 2003; 249344 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 5th Annual Beckman Scholars Symposium, "Our Energy Challenge", July 24-26, 2003; 249343 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - DARPA Moletronics Principal Investigator's Meeting, July 28, 2003; 249342 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Nano Summit Conference, July 31, 2003; 249341 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - nGRC: Clusters, Nanocrystals, and Nanostructures, "Energy", August 3, 2003; 249340 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Argonne National Laboratory Nanoscience Research Summer School, August 5, 2003; 249339 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - 39th IUPAC Congress (cancelled), August 10-15, 2003; 249338 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - NASA URETI Review (cancelled), August 19-21, 2003; 249337 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - SRC TechCon '03, "21st Century Energy Initiatives: The Role of Nanotechnology", August 25-27, 2003; 249336 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Institute for Soldier Nanotechnologies Science Advisory Board (ISN SAB), "Nanotechnology and Energy", September 4-5, 2003; 249335 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - ACS National Meeting, September 7, 2003; 249334 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - World Nano-Economic Congress, "Nanotechnology and Energy", September 10, 2003; 249333 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Integrated Nanosystems 2003 (cancelled), September 19, 2003; 249332 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Columbia University Nanocenter Seminar, "Our Energy Challenge", September 24, 2003; 249331 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Energy Forum (cancelled), September 25, 2003; 249330 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - BP Leadership Workshop, October 6-7, 2003; 249329 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Senator Hutchinson Scientific Advisory Committee, October 8, 2003; 249328 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Oesper Award Banquet (cancelled), October 10, 2003; 249327 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Sverdrup Visiting Science Lecture (cancelled), October 13-14, 2003; 249326 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - HESTEC 2003 Conference (cancelled), October 13-16, 2003; 249325 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Basic Energy Sciences Advisory Committee (BESAC) (cancelled), October 20, 2003; 249324 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Kansas City Civic Council Meeting, October 23, 2003; 249323 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - DURINT Review, October 24, 2003; 249322 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - The Houston Club, "Nanotechnology and Energy", October 27, 2003; 249321 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - CAST Keynote Houston, October 31, 2003; 249320 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society (Neal Lane Symposium), November 1-2, 2003; 249319 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Clearfield Endowed Lecture Series, November 4, 2003; 249318 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - SGA Executive Conference, November 11, 2003; 249317 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Air Force HBCU/MI Major Thrust Program, November 12, 2003; 249316 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - World Energy Investment Outlook Luncheon, November 14, 2003; 249315 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - M.D. Anderson Convocation, November 14, 2003; 249314 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Forum: Creativity in the 21st Century (cancelled), November 16, 2003; 249313 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - GE/Plug Power, November 17, 2003; 249312 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Siemans Westinghouse Math Science & Technology Competition (cancelled), November 22, 2003; 249311 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - White House, December 2, 2003; 249310 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Texas Academy of Science, Engineering, and Medicine Conference, January 6-7, 2004; 249309 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Rice Nanotechnology Innovation Forum: "Nanotechnology: Creating the Next Energy Revolution", January 16, 2004; 249308 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - River Oaks Breakfast Club, Janaury 22, 2004; 249307 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Texas Research Board Meeting, January 28, 2004; 249306 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Texas Academy Board Meeting, February 14, 2004; 249305 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Basic Energy Sciences Advisory Committee (BESAC), February 23-24, 2004; 249304 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Edward Rosenfeld Discover Magazine, February 27, 2004; 249303 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Intel Meeting, March 3, 2004; 249302 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Nanohealth Alliance Meeting, March 5, 2003; 249301 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - General Paul Nielson Meeting, March 11, 2004; 249300 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Rice Distinguished Lecture Series: "Buckytubes: From Discovery to Production", March 12, 2004; 249299 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Case Media Fellowship: "Increasing Energy Capacity", March 15, 2004; 249298 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - DOE Nanotechnology Initiative Conference: "Nanotechnology for Continental Energy System", March 16-18, 2004; 249297 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Technology Review Interview: Peter Fairley, March 22, 2004; 249296 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Austin American Statesman Interview: Mark Lisheron, March 24, 2004; 249295 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Rice Board of Trustees Meeting: "Nanotech Update", March 24, 2004; 249294 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - University of Chicago Conference Call- Tom Rosenbaum, March 25, 2004; 249293 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Nanotechnology Foundation of Texas Briefing, March 26, 2004; 249292 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - AOS Laboratory Tour, March 29, 2004; 249291 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - WNYC Live Interview, March 30, 2004; 249290 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - National Nanotechnology Initiative, March 31-April 2, 2004; 249289 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - SWNT Conference Call, April 6, 2004; 249288 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - CNI Dinner- Motorola, April 7, 2004; 249287 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Baker Institute Student Forum: "Scientific Integrity and Policy Making", April 7, 2004; 249286 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - EPSRC Visit (cancelled), April 8, 2004; 249285 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Charles Browning/ Air Force Conference Call, April 9, 2004; 249284 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - South Texas Nuclear Power Plant Tour, April 10, 2004; 249283 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - NASA- General Howell, April 12, 2004; 249282 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - PBS Interview: Anna Jhirad, April 13, 2004; 249281 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Gulf Coast Power Association, April 14, 2004; 249280 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Nanohealth meetings, April 18-20, 2004; 249279 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Valley Forward Livability Summit, April 22, 2004; 249278 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee Hearing: "Future Energy Challenges", April 27, 2004; 249277 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - National Junior Science and Humanities Symposium: "The Brave New World of Buckytubes", April 29-30, 2004; 249276 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Eric Roston Interview, May 6, 2004; 249275 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - University of Richmond Honorary Doctor of Science degree, May 9, 2004; 249274 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Alliance for Nanohealth Workshop, May 14, 2004; 249273 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - DARPA/NASA meeting, May 19-20, 2004; 249272 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - CINT Groundbreaking Ceremony and meeting, May 26, 2004; 249271 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Conference Defining the Future: "Future World Energy Requirements and the Role of Carbon Nanotechnology", May 29-June 3, 2004; 249270 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Technion- Israel Institute of Technology Honorary Doctorate of Science, June 14, 2004; 249269 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - APG Meeting, June 22, 2004; 249268 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - DOE Nanosummit: "Nanoscience and the Energy Future", June 23-24, 2004; 249267 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - DARPA/NIST Meetings, June 30-July 2, 2004; 249266 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - WPAFB Meeting, July 7, 2004; 251849 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Texas Education Board, July 15, 2004; 252343 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University Science and Engineering Institute, July 26-27, 2004; 252344 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - DOE/NSRC (cancelled), August 2-3, 2004; 252353 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - NRO Technology Seminar: The Brave New World of Buckytubes, August 4, 2004; 252354 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - BESAC Energy Science Advisory Committee (cancelled), August 5-6, 2004; 253352 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Jie Liu Collaboration /DARPA Project, August 12-13, 2004; 253356 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Senator Hutchison Press Conference/Alliance for Nanohealth Funding, August 18, 2004; 253472 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - ACS Presidential Event Symposium: Fuels for the Future, August 24, 2004; 257678 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Documentary: Nobelity- Conversations with Beautiful Minds, August 31, 2004; 257679 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - NCI Alliance for Nanotechnology in Cancer, September 13, 2004; 257680 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Purdue University: Our Energy Challenge, September 15, 2004; 257681 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - NIST and Alliance for NanoHealth, September 21, 2004; 257682 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Case Western Reserve Frontiers in Chemistry:Our Energy Challenge, September 23, 2004; 257683 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Tuskeegee University Energy and Nanotechnology, October 3, 2004; 257684 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - DARPA SWNT Amplifier Demonstration Project, October 6, 2004; 257818 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Rice Energy Solar Workshop, October 15-17, 2004; 257819 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory, October 19-20, 2004; 257820 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - General Howell Visit to Nanotechnology Laboratory, November 2, 2004; 257821 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - SemiNanoForum 2004: Our Energy Challenge, November 15, 2004; 257822 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Wright Patterson Air Force Base: Dr. Charles Browning, November 18, 2004; 260049 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Materials Research Society: Nanotechnology for Energy Prosperity, December 2, 2004; 260050 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - BESAC meeting (cancelled), December 6-7, 2004; 260051 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - AFRL/ML - WBI Collaboration, December 8, 2004; 260052 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - IEEE International Electronic Device meeting: Our Energy Challenge, December 14, 2004; 260053 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - SSAT Development Team, December 16, 2004; 260054 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - 31st Photovoltaic Specialists Conference, January 3-4, 2005; 260055 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - The Academy of Medicine, Engineering and Science of Texas, January 6-7, 2005; 260056 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - University of Texas at Austin Plan II Honors Program, February 2, 2005; 260057 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Alliance for NanoHealth Meeting, February 4, 2005; 260058 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - GE Housto Symposium, February 11, 2005; 260059 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - 2005 NanoTech Summit: WPAFB, March 1-3, 2005; 260060 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Georgia Tech Carey Lecturer (cancelled), March 9-10, 2005; 260061 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - ACS NanoTechnology meeting (cancelled), March 13-17, 2005; 260062 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - DARPA SWNT Amplifier meeting, March 22-23, 2005; 260063 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Stanford University Colloquium (cancellled), March 31, 2005; 260064 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Illinois Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, April 3-4, 2005; 260065 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - NASA/Rice SWNT Workshop, April 8-12, 2005; 260066 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - FOrt Bend Economic Development Council, April 21, 2005; 260067 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - AOS Tour of CNL Lab, April 25, 2005; 260068 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Advanced Energy Consortium (cancelled), April 27, 2005; 260069 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Hope College Distinguished Alumni Award (cancelled), May 7, 2005; 260070 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - PTV Sciences Board meeting, May 18, 2005; 260071 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Alliance for NanoHealth Working Group, June 2, 2005; 260072 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - National Geographic Photo Shoot, June 9-10, 2005; 260073 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - DARPA SWNT Amplifier/Northrup-Grumman meeting, June 23, 2005; 260074 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Brookhaven CFN Ground Breaking (cancelled), July 1, 2005; 260075 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - NanoTech Summit, July 27, 2005; 260076 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - CNT Polymer Composites International Conference (cancelled), September 4-7, 2005; 260077 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Dow Science & Technology Conference (cancelled), October 5, 2005; 260078 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - University of Wisconsin Energy Seminar (cancelled), October 24-25, 2005; 260079 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Series XIV: Projects and Administration, 1996-2005
  - Sub-Series A: Projects
    - Carbon Nanotechnologies Inc. (CNI), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Center for Integrated Nanotechnologies, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Center for Nanophase Materials Sciences, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Governor's Council on Science & Biotechnology Development, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Energy Task Force, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Rice Quantum Institute (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Cool Chips PLC, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Pinto Technology Ventures, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Space Education Inc., 2004 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Zyvex Energy, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series B: Administration
    - Press photos, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Nanotechnology Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Sarofim Chair Committee, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Welch Chair Committee, 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Center for Nanoscale Science & Technology brochure, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Cees Decker, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Congressman Ken Bentson tour, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - V. S. Letokhov, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Chao Chair in Chemistry, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - John Yates, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Carbon Nanotechnology Lab opening, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Ivan Bekey, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Steven Wax, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Nominations, 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Senator Kay Bailey Hutchison, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Ken Deffeyes, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - History of Carbon Nanotubes, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Joshua Jortner, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Press articles, 1996-2005 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Interview transcript (with Gary Taubes) (Box 12, Folder 81)
- Series XV: Personal, 1985-2006
  - Southwest High School, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hope College history, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Chemical Heritage Foundation Donation, 2004-2006 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Smalley wedding invitation, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Smalley portrait (copy) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hope College Memorial Book, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Smalley memorial services (1 of 2), 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Smalley memorial services (2 of 2), 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Obituaries, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Awards, 1992-2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Madison Marshall Award, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - John Stauffer Lecturer, Stanford University, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Texas Academy of Science Distinguished Scientist Award, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - West Point Society of Greater Houston, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Highly Cited Researchers, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Who's Who, 1996-2000 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Nobel Laureate Award articles, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - American Chemical Society Southwest Regional Award, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Dupont-Marshall Lectureship, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - IR Laboratory of the Year (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - John Scott Medal (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Kilby Award, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Smalley photographs, 1985-2002 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook photographs, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Tribute videos, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Series XVI: Oversize, 1943-2006
  - Hope College Distinguished Alumni Award, 2005 (Box 14, Item 1)
  - Framed Photograph (Box 14, Item 2)
  - U.S. flag flown over the Capitol in memory of Smalley (Congressman John Culberson), 2006 (Box 14, Item 3)
  - U.S. flag flown over the Capitol in honor of Smalley (Congressman Ken Bentson) (Box 14, Item 4)
  - State Senate Proclamation (Senator Rodney Ellis), 2007 (Box 14, Item 5)
  - Smalley photograph (Box 14, Item 6)
  - Scrapbook pages, 1996-2003 (Box 14, Item 7)
  - Posters (Box 14, Item 8)
  - Family scrapbook pages, 1943-1965 (Box 15, Item 1)
  - Baby/childhood scrapbook, 1943-1963 (Box 16, Item 1)
  - Nobel Prize congratulation letters scrapbook, 1996 (Box 16, Item 2)
  - Congressional Record, 1997-2005 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Memorabilia, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - National Geographic Nanotechnology photographs, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Arthur D. Little Lectureship in Chemistry, Northeastern University, 1996 (Box 16, Item 6)
  - Awards, 1992-2007 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Honorary Doctorates, 1992-2004 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Series XVII: Photographs, 1996-2005, undated; 1.78 Gigabytes
  Scope and Contents
  This digital object contains photographs of Richard Smalley at events honoring his discovery of the Carbon 60 molecule and related magazine articles.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This digital object can be accessed with the aip number (MS0490aip_001) in the Reading Room of the Woodson Research Center, Fondren Library, Rice University.
- Series XVIII: Nobel Prize Certificate, 1996
  - Nobel Prize Certificate, 1996 (Box 18)